freshersalary.com 2011-05-19

# freshersalary.com - Jobs in India, Mumbai, Bangalore, Chennai, Delhi, Pune

FresherSalary.com   
**PRIVACY POLICY**   
This Privacy Policy ("Policy") describes [http://www.freshersalary.com](http://www.freshersalary.com/) collection and use of personal information from Internet users visiting the website. By using the Site, you are accepting the practices described in this Policy and agree to accept the terms of the Policy as currently posted on the Site.  Any changes to this Policy will be effective upon posting. 

**  INFORMATION COLLECTED**  
Personally identifiable information ("PII") is data that identifies a specific individual, such as name, address, telephone number, email address, and birth date. web servers automatically collect non-personally identifiable information  about Site visitors, such as demographic information (age, gender, city or state), and "click stream data." Click stream data includes information such as a Site visitor's IP address, web pages viewed as well as date and time, and browser and platform type. These automated server functions do not collect this information in a manner intended to identify a Site visitor. 

Our servers uses a common Internet technology called "cookies" to collect data about Site visitors. A cookie is a small text file written to an Internet user's browser that contains unique information about the Internet user. Cookies permit the Site to recall information from a Site visitor's previous visits and customize the Site for the visitor's future use.  Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. 

  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).) 

**HOW INFORMATION IS USED**  
We use data for a variety of purposes, including the administration and operation of the Site, designing and developing new products and services, and generally improving the overall quality of your experience with the Site and services.  
**  
CONTACT INFORMATION**   
We welcomes your questions and comments about security and privacy. If you have any questions or concerns, please send an e-mail to us. We will investigate and attempt to respond to any question or resolve complaints and disputes in a timely fashion.
